A Guide to the Correspondence of the Director of the Virginia Dept. of Medical Assistance Services, 1982-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series IV: Correspondence [Accession 41103], 1993-1999, Extent: 6 cu. ft. (6 boxes). (Box 1-6)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 July 1-12 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 July 12-20 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 July 20-23 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 July 23-30 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 August 1-11 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 August 11-27 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 August 27-31 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 September (Box 6, Folder 2-5)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 October 1-8 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 October 12-19 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 October 20-28 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 November 1-5 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 November 8-17 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 November 18-30 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 December 1-6 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 December 7-10 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 December 10-15 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 1999 December 15-30 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Series V: Correspondence [Accession 43704], 1995-2002, Extent: 11 cu. ft. (11 boxes). (Box 1-11)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 January 1-13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 January 14-31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 February 1-7 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 February 8-15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 February 16-29 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 March 2-16 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 March 17-28 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 March 29-30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 April 1-13 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 April 14-30 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 May 1-15 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 May 16-31 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 June 1-16 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 June 17-26 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 June 27-30 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 July 1-14 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 July 15-20 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 July 21-31 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 August 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 August 11-31 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 September 1-7 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 September 8-21 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 September 22-27 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 September 28-29 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 October 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 October 11-19 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 October 20-31 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 November 1-6 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 November 7-14 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 November 15-30 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 December 1-6 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 December 7-14 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 December 15-19 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2000 December 20-31 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Weekly reports, Robert W. Lauterberg, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Weekly reports, Dennis G. Smith, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Weekly reports, Dennis G. Smith, 2000-2001 January (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2001 January 1-5 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Dennis G. Smith, Correspondence, 2001 January 6-9 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 January 10-19 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 January 20-31 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 February 1-13 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 February 14-20 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 February 21-28 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 March 1-2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 March 2 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 March 3-15 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 March 16-30 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 April 1-10 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 April 11-18 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 April 19-24 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 April 25-30 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - C. Mack Brankley, Correspondence, 2001 May 1-9 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 May 10-18 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 May 19-23 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 May 25-31 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 June 1-8 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 June 9-20 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 June 21-27 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 June 28-30 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 July 1-9 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 July 10-17 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 July 18-27 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 July 27-31 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 August 1-6 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 August 6-14 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 August 14 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 August 14-29 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 August 29 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 August 29-31 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 September 1-7 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 September 7-15 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 September 16-19 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 September 19 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 September 19-26 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 September 27-30 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 1-5 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 5 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 5-11 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 12-15 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 15-16 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 16-19 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 20-23 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 23-25 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 25 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 25-29 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 October 29-31 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 November 1-5 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 November 5-8 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 November 9-14 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 November 14-19 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 November 19 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 November 20-30 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 December 1-7 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 December 8-12 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 December 13-17 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 December 19-20 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2001 December 21-31 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2002 January 1-9 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2002 January 10-23 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Eric S. Bell, Correspondence, 2002 January 24-31 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 February 1-14 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 February 15-22 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 February 22-28 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 March 1-6 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 March 8-13 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 March 14-20 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 March 20 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 March 20-28 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 April 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 April 10-16 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 April 19-30 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 May 1-10 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 May 13-21 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 May 21-31 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 June 1-12 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 June 12-20 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 June 20-24 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 June 24 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 June 27-28 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 July 1-8 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 July 9-11 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 July 11-15 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 July 16-22 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 July 22-25 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 July 25-31 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 August 1-9 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 August 9-22 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 August 23-27 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 August 27-30 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 September 3-6 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 September 6-20 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 September 23-30 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 October 1-7 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 October 7-24 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 October 24-31 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 November 1-6 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 November 6-13 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 November 13-15 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 November 15-21 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 November 21-27 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 December 2-10 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 December 10-18 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2002 December 18-31 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Medicaid Letters [No. 96-02 - 97-08], 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Medicaid Letters [No. 97-09 - 97-35], 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Weekly reports (Dennis Smith and Eric Bell), 2001 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Weekly reports (Eric Bell and Patrick Finnerty), 2002 (Box 9, Folder 12-13)
  - HCFA-CMS (Health Care Financing Administration, Centers for Medicaid and Medicare Services), 1995 January-February (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995 February-March (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995 March-April (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995 May (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995 June (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995 July (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995 August (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995 September (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995 October (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995 November-December (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1995, Misc. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Medicaid Letters [No. 95-01 - 95-44], 1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Medicaid Letters [No. 95-45 - 95-75], 1995 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1996 January-February (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1996 February-March (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1996 April (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1996 April-May (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1996 May-June (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1996 June-July (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1996 July-September (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1996 October-December (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - HCFA-CMS, 1996 December (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Series VI: Correspondence [Accession 44650], 2001-2006, Extent: 10.35 cu. ft. (11 boxes). (Box 1-11)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 January 3-11 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 January 11-31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 February (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 March 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 March 11-31 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 April 1-14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 April 15-29 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 May 2-9 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 May 9-12 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 May 13-23 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 May 24-31 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 June 1-14 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 June 15-30 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 July 1-12 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 July 13-29 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 August 1-10 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 August 11-24 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 August 24 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 August 25-31 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 September 1-13 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 September 15-30 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 October 3-11 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 October 12-31 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 November 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 November 14-17 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 November 18-30 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 December 1-14 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 December 15-18 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2005 December 19-30 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 January 1-10 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 January 10-22 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 January 23-31 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 February 5-19 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 February 19-28 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 March 1-7 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 March 7-14 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 March 14-20 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 March 21-28 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 March 28-31 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 April 1-8 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 April 8-23 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 April 24-30 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 May 1-12 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 May 13-30 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 June 2-10 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 June 10-16 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 June 18-30 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 July 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 July 15-31 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 August 1-8 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 August 8-19 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 August 19-30 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 September 1-15 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 September 16-30 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 October 2-22 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 October 22-24 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 October 25-31 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 November 3-13 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 November 15-26 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 December 1-17 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2003 December 18-31 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 January (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 February 2-6 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 February 9-27 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 March 1-12 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 March 15-31 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 April 1-20 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 April 21-30 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 May 3-14 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 May 18-28 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 May 18-28 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 June 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 June 16-24 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 June 25-30 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 July 1-8 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 July 9-21 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 July 22-30 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 August 2-13 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 August 16-23 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 August 24-30 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 September 3-13 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 September 14-30 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 October 1-13 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 October 14-29 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 November (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2004 December (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 January (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 February 1-15 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 February 15-27 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 March 1-17 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 March 20-30 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 March 30-31 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 April 3-4 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 April 5-28 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 May 2-16 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 May 19-31 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 June 1-13 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 June 13-30 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 July 5-25 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 July 25-31 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 August (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 September 1-15 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 September 18-29 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 October 2-12 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 October 13-23 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 October 23 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 October 24-31 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 November (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 December 1-12 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Patrick W. Finnerty, Correspondence, 2006 December 13-29 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - CMS (Center for Medicaid and State Operations), Correspondence, 2001 January (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 January (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 February (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 March (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 March (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 April (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 May (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 June (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 July (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 July (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 August (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 September (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 September (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 September-October (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 November (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 November (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2001 December (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 January (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 February (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 March (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 March (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 April (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 May (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 May (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 June (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 July (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 August (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 September (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - CMS, Correspondence, 2002 October (Box 8, Folder 15)